مرحباً، أنا إدي
مُجتمعنا يسمى إدي هَب
نحن نؤمن بأن التعاون يأتي أولاً و الكود يأتي ثانياً
نحن مجتمع شامل مفتوح المصدر الذي يركز على دعم بعضنا
لا يهم أين أنت في مسيرتك
تذكر، حتى لو كنت تملِك خبرة شهر واحد
هناك شخص الآن في مكانك قبل شهر
Helping others is a great way to learn and
grow your network
We have my YouTube where you will find lots
of tutorials about open source and GitHub
I also do live streams getting you involved
in open source and finding you the green squares
Also I bring awesome guests on there
to hang out with us
We also have a GitHub organisation that you
can join
Just raise an issue on the support repo with
the type "invite me to the organisation"
And the GitHub Action will do all the magic
and do all the rest, and send you an invitation
Remember if you would like other people to
see you are part of our organisation
You have to make it public on your profile,
only you can do that
We have many projects in our GitHub organisation
from Discord bots written in typescript to
react frontends
And everything in between
If you want to get involved our community
will help you
You can also get your open source project
review by the community and by me
And you guessed it by raising an issue on
our support repo with the issue type "review
my open source project"
If you want to chat between YouTube videos
and live streams and your open source green
squares
We also have a Discord where you can come
and join the conversation
With many exciting things going on and so
much more to come
If you want to learn more about open source,
collaborate and improve your technical and
your communication skills
Join our community to accelerate your career
Looking forward to chatting with you soon